http://www.wisconsincheese.com/privacy-policy

Search
Loading
Privacy Policy
INTRODUCTION
The policies below are intended to clearly inform our users about our privacy practices and procedures and are applicable to WisconsinCheese.com (previously named EatWisconsinCheese.com), WisconsinDairy.org (previously named DairyDoingMore.or WMMB.com), Cheeselandia.com, WisconsinDairyCouncil.com, WisconsinCheeseTools.com, (previously named WisconsinCheeseRetail.com and WisconsinCheeseFoodservice.com), GrilledCheeseAcademy.com and CheeseAndBurger.com.
As part of the registration, operation and customization features of WisconsinCheese.com, we gather certain types of information from users. We would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with them, and how to correct or change the information. Please review this privacy policy when you enter the website to keep aware of any policy changes.
WisconsinCheese.com does not share any personal information collected through the website with third parties.
INFORMATION COLLECTED BY WISCONSINCHEESE.COM
WisconsinCheese.com collects two types of information from users: personal data such as name, phone, and e-mail addresses; and non-personal data such as information about traffic patterns on WisconsinCheese.com (for example, how many users log on to WisconsinCheese.com on a daily basis).
PERSONAL DATA
Some personal data such as name, phone, postal address, e-mail address and business type are collected during registration or through other form submissions on our site.
NON-PERSONAL DATA
Some data we collect contains non-personal information. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site or advertisement. We may use this information for various purposes, including system administration and enhancement and to collect information about the volume of use of different features available on WisconsinCheese.com.
CHILDREN AND PRIVACY
WisconsinCheese.com has no intention of collecting personal information from children (i.e., individuals under the age of 13). If a child has provided us with personal information, WisconsinCheese.com asks that a parent or guardian of the child contact us at info@EatWisconsinCheese.com if they would like the information submitted by a child deleted from our database. EatWisconsinCheese.com will use reasonable efforts to delete such information from its database.
COOKIES
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. EatWisconsinCheese.com uses cookies to collect information. Cookies allow EatWisconsinCheese.com to measure activity on the site and to make improvements and updates based on which areas are popular and which are not. Cookies are used to improve your user experience. For example, the cookie allows you to have the option of saving your user name and password which eliminates the need for you to enter the information every time you visit hello@wisconsincheese.com. (We do not recommend saving your user name and password if you use your computer in a shared environment.) In addition, our site may request the cookie from your browser so that we can retrieve the stored personal information to fill out forms so you do not have to manually enter the information each time. We may also store data on your cookie based on options you make on certain forms to enable us to customize information based on your criteria.
Please note that with most browsers, a user can set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also usually set the browser not to accept cookies at all. By not accepting cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all features of WisconsinCheese.com.
USE OF INFORMATION
WisconsinCheese.com uses both the personal and non-personal information we collect for a variety of purposes. For example, we use your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better products and service. Specifically, we use your information to communicate back to you, to update you on programs, services and benefits, and to personalize our website for you. We also use the non-personal information to provide aggregate data reports to our Board of Directors and other interested parties. WisconsinCheese.com does not share any personal information collected through the website with third parties.
CHANGING USER INFORMATION
To correct or change your registration information click on the "My Account" link on the top of each WisconsinCheese.com page. To have us correct other personal information that you believe may be incorrect contact us at (608) 836-8820
hello@wisconsincheese.com.
SECURITY
WisconsinCheese.com is committed to taking reasonable steps to ensure the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
YOUR CONSENT
By using this website, you consent to our use of your personal and non-personal data as specified above. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
CONCERNS AND COMMENTS
Your privacy concerns are important to us. Please email or write to us with any further questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy.
Dairy Farmers of Wisconsin
8418 Excelsior Drive
Madison, Wisconsin 53717
(608) 836-8820
hello@wisconsincheese.com
Cheese
Our Cheese
Find Cheese
More
Why Wisconsin?
Grate. Pair. Share.
Art of Cheese Festival
The Cheese Life Blog
Wedding Cakes
About
Contact
Join Us
Media
My Account
You'll know it's one of ours when you see the badge.
Need help? Say Hello
(608) 836-8820
Hello@WisconsinCheese.com
Wisconsin Cheese Newsletter
Enter Your Email
All Things Cheese Newsletter
About
Contact
Media
©   Dairy Farmers of Wisconsin Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Sitemap
In Wisconsin, we make more flavors, varieties, and styles of cheese than anywhere else in the world. We believe in tradition, producing everything from Italian classics, like parmesan and ricotta, to swiss cheese and cheddar varieties. But every Wisconsin cheesemaker is an innovator as well, which is why we have so many Wisconsin originals, like colby and muenster. Whether it’s a grilled cheese sandwich, potatoes au gratin, or a charcuterie board, Wisconsin cheese makes every dish and recipe tastier.
